Guide to the American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1899-2008.
American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records,
- Series XI. Publications
  - Proceedings: Conference of College Teachers of Textiles and Clothing - Central Region, 1954-1956 (Box 231)
  - Proceedings on Training of Family Economists for College Teaching and Research, 1956 (Box 231)
  - Proceedings of a Conference: Using Family Expenditure and Related Data in Teaching Financial Management, 1958 (Box 231)
  - AHEA learning packages, Pacesetter presentation, grad program guidelines, circa 1970 (Box 231)
  - The Home Economist in Business: A Profile Study of Education, Skills, Employment, 1976 (Box 231)
  - The Balancing Act: Thinking Globally Acting Locally, Proceedings of a Workshop, 1985 (Box 231)
  - AHEA Monograph Series, 1993 (Box 231)
  - Profiles of Full-Time Employed Home Economists, AHEA Survey (Box 231)
  - Proceedings, Conference on Teaching Home Management, AHEA Family Economics-Home Management Section, 1962 (Box 231)
  - Proceedings of Workshop on Home Economics in Small Departments and Departments Located in Liberal Arts Colleges or Units of the College, AHEA Colleges and Universities Section, 1959 (Box 231)
  - Proceedings, Conference on Training of Family Economists for College Teaching and Research, AHEA Family Economics-Home Management Section, 1956 (Box 231)
  - References to Help the Teacher in Curriculum Change, 1963 (Box 231)
  - Public Relations in Homemaking Education Depends in You, 1952; 2 copies (Box 231)
  - Reach for a Star: Choose Home Economics, 1948; 2 copies (Box 231)
  - Rehabilitation of the Physically Handicapped in Homemaking Activities, Proceedings of a Workshop, 1963 (Box 231)
  - A Research Foundation for the American Home, 1957 (Box 231)
  - New Resources in Research, 1961 (Box 231)
  - Research Related to Design, Housing and Equipment, Home Furnishings, and Interior Design, 1942-1965 (Box 231)
  - Contemporary Issues in Home Economics, 1965 (Box 231)
  - Examination of Home Economics Textbooks for Sexist Bias, 1976-06 (Box 231)
  - A Content Analysis and Reading Ease Scores of the Journal of Home Economics, 1909-1968 (Master's thesis, University of Wisconsin), 1972 (Box 231)
  - Educating the Teen-Ager in Human Relations Management of Resources (papers from the 56th AHEA annual meeting), 1965 (Box 231)
  - La Evaluacion Sobre el Taller de la Generacion de Ingresos Para las Mujeres Rurales en America Latina en 1984, 1987 (Box 231)
  - Home Economics and Women in Development: Proceedings of AHEA Pre-AWID Conference Seminar, 1983; 2 copies (Box 231)
  - Report of the Pilot AHEA-RSA Internship for Home Economists in Rehabilitation, 1970 (Box 231)
  - The Adventure of Accumulating a Collection, Mary F. Patterson, 1935 (Box 231)
  - Rehabilitation of the Physically Handicapped in Homemaking Activities: Proceedings of a Workshop, 1963 (Box 231)
  - Expanding the Services of the Home Economist in Rehabilitation, workshop proceedings, 1960 (Box 231)
  - Dynamic Planning for Uncertain Times: Living in an Era of Economic Uncertainty, 1981 (Box 231)
  - Economic Decisions of Families: Security for the Elderly and Labor Force Participation of Women, 1983 (Box 231)
  - The Household as Producer-a Look Beyond the Market, 1979 (Box 231)
  - Student Guide Book (Box 231)
  - Proceedings of the 1976 Nutrition Education Workshop, 2 copies (Box 231)
  - Publications on family living and family relations (Box 231)
  - Home Economics and Education for Family Life, 1932 (Box 231)
  - A Student Study Guide for use with Living Together in the Family and Pictures of Family Life (Box 231)
  - Training Volunteer Nutrition Consultants for Head Start: A Program of the American Home Economics Association, 1987 (Box 231)
  - The Story of the New England Kitchen, 1890 (Box 233)
  - Lessons in Cooking, parts 1 & 3, American School of Home Economics, Chicago, 1911 (Box 233)
  - America's Gifts to the Old World by Atwater and Langworthy, 1915 (Box 233)
  - Syllabus of Home Economics, 1913 (Box 233)
  - The First Home Economist (Box 233)
  - Thrift by Household Accounting and Weekly Cash Record Forms, 1918 (Box 233)
  - A Study of the Energy Expenditure and Mechanical Efficiency of Young Girls and Adult Women by Ethel Thompson, 1940 (Box 233)
  - 25 Years of a Great Idea by Kathryn Stone, 1946 (Box 233)
  - A History of the League Program by Kathryn Stone, 1949 (Box 233)
  - The Chambers Fireless Cooking Gas Range [brochure] (Box 233)
  - First Annual Report of the School Lunch Committee of the Home and School League, 1911 (Box 233)
  - School Lunches in Philadelphia, 1913-1914 (Box 233)
  - Report of the National League for the Protection of the Family, 1912 (Box 233)
  - Early Dietetics by Sarah Tyson Rorer, 1934 (Box 233)
  - Home Makers Course by the Texas Congress of Mothers and Parent-Teachers Association, 1915 (Box 233)
  - Health Alphabet postcard (Box 233)
  - American Homemakers Incorporated calendar, 1928-02 (Box 233)
  - Bulletin, Chicago School of Sanitary Instruction, 4 November 1911 (Box 233)
  - The School Lunch [Boston, Massachusetts], 1920 (Box 233)
  - The Art of Cooking by Edward Atkinson, 1889 (Box 233)
  - The Aladdin Oven and the Tub Oven. How to Save Coal., 1902 (Box 233)
  - Symposium on School Feeding. The Psychological Clinic, 1912 (Box 233)
  - The Psychological Clinic, v.3 no.8, 1910 (Box 233)
  - An Ideal Kitchen. Miss Parloa's Kitchen Companion., 1887 (Box 233)
  - Master Allen's Prophecy. By Sallie Joy White., 1888 (Box 233)
  - The Thing To Do. Extracts from a Phi Beta Kappa address to college women, by Whitelaw Reid., 1903-06-08 (Box 233)
  - Report of a Two Years' Experiment in Social Economics. Boston, 1903. Household Aid Company, Committee on Domestic Economy, Women's Education Association. (Box 233)
  - Plain Words About Food: the Rumford Kitchen Leaflets, 1899 (Box 233)
  - Articles and information about Count Rumford and the Rumford Kitchen (Box 233)
  - The Rumford Kitchen Leaflets, no. 1-3, 5-15, 20, 1893 (Box 233)
  - "Cost of Foods from Prison to Palace Hotel," Annie Dewey, Bulletin of the AHEA, series 4 no. 3 (Box 233)
  - Recipe booklets and brochures, circa 1917 (Box 234)
  - Lists of USDA bulletins and circulars (Box 234)
  - Canning-Drying Series sheet. USDA., 1918 (Box 234)
  - USDA Farmers' Bulletin, 1894-1918; 6 folders (Box 234)
  - USDA Farmers' Bulletin, 1894-1918; 1 folders (Box 236)
  - USDA Bulletin, 1915-1924; 2 folders (Box 236)
  - Bulletin. USDA Division of Chemistry., 1889 (Box 236)
  - Bulletin. USDA Bureau of Chemistry., 1902-1908 (Box 236)
  - Circular. USDA Office of the Secretary., 1918 (Box 236)
  - Reprints from Yearbook of Department of Agriculture, 1901, 1911-1914, 1919 (Box 236)
  - USDA Farmers' Bulletin and Bulletin; USFA Fuel Facts., 1914-1918 (Box 236)
  - Circular. USDA Office of Experiment Stations., 1909-1912 (Box 236)
  - Bulletin. USDA Office of Experiment Stations., 1896-1899 (Box 236)
  - Bulletin. USDA Office of Experiment Stations., 1897-1905; 6 folders (Box 248)
  - Bulletin. USDA Office of Experiment Stations., 1905-1912; 3 folders (Box 249)
  - Agencies for the Sale of Cooked Food Without Profit. Council of National Defense, Woman's Committee., 1919 (Box 249)
  - The Daily Meals of School Children by Caroline Hunt, 1909 (Box 249)
  - Education for the Home by Benjamin Andrews, 1915 (Box 249)
  - Thrift leaflets, no. 1-20, circa 1918 (Box 249)
  - Bureau of Education circulars on home economics, 1917-1919 (Box 249)
  - United States Food Administration booklets and pamphlets, circa 1918 (Box 249)
  - Food Saving and Sharing. United States Food Administration., 1918 (Box 249)
  - Food Thrift Series, no. 1-5, 1917 (Box 249)
  - United States Food Leaflet, no. 1-7, circa 1917 (Box 249)
  - The Housewife and the War leaflets. USDA., circa 1917 (Box 249)
  - A Brief History and Summary of Thirty Years of 4-H Club Work in North Carolina, 1909-1939 (Box 264)
  - Historical Appraisal of Subject Matter Project: Food Conservation and Marketing, 1914-1939 (Box 264)
  - Publications on home demonstration and extension work, 1913-1939 (Box 264)
  - Extension bulletins and circulars. Ohio State University., 1914-1918 (Box 264)
  - Home economics bulletins and circulars, and emergency leaflets. Iowa State College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts., 1917-1920 (Box 264)
  - Home economics laboratory manual. University of Wisconsin., 1911 (Box 264)
  - Bulletin. Oregon Agricultural College Extension Service., 1917 (Box 264)
  - Booklet on Cuban rural schools (Spanish) (Box 264)
  - Extension circulars. Utah Agricultural College., 1912-1919 (Box 264)
  - Extension leaflet. Purdue University., 1914 (Box 264)
  - Bulletin. Kansas State Agricultural College., 1914 (Box 264)
  - Extension bulletin. Minnesota Farmers' Library. University of Minnesota., 1913 (Box 264)
  - Publications by the Children's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor., 1915-1927 (Box 264)
  - Domestic Economy in Foreign Countries
    - General domestic sciences, 1925-1930; 2 folders (Box 264)
    - General domestic sciences, 1875-1909; 2 folders (Box 273)
    - Cooking and laundry, circa 1870-1939 (Box 273)
    - Health, circa 1870-1939 (Box 273)
    - Sewing, textiles, circa 1870-1939 (Box 273)
    - Manual training, circa 1870-1939 (Box 273)
  - Parents and the Latch Key, 1936 (Box 273)
  - "Home economics is for men too" (term paper by Wilburn J. Hollis), 1964 (Box 273)
  - "An historical survey of the role of men in the home economics movement in the United States," by Helen Holweck, 1972 (Box 273)
  - "The history of nutrition and home economics in the University of California, Berkeley 1914-1962" by Agnes Fay Morgan (Box 273)
  - The History of Home Economics. By Hazel T. Craig, 1945 (Box 273)
  - General information about metric system, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Analyses of going metric, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Recommendations for metric conversion, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Impacts of metric usage, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Metric education, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Tables, charts, pamphlets, circa 1970 (Box 245)
  - Metric Editorial Guide (Box 245)
  - Position Papers on Career Education Prepared for the National Conference on Career Education: Implications for Minorities, 1973 (Box 245)
  - A Job Development Program in the Home and Apartment Maintenance Industry - A Business Opportunity, 1966 (Box 245)
  - Publications on careers in home economics, 3 folders (Box 245)
  - Publications on careers in food and nutrition (Box 245)
  - Various nutrition publications (Box 245)
  - Procedures for Calculating Nutritive Values of Home-Prepared Foods, 1963 (Box 245)
  - Family Food Plans and Food Costs: For nutritionists and other leaders who develop or use food plans, 1962 (Box 245)
  - Composition of Foods Used in Far Eastern Countries, March 1952 (Box 245)
  - Food Composition Data Description of punched cards and magnetic tape, 1972-04 (Box 245)
  - Nutritive Value of Common Foods in Percent of RDA and U.S. RDA, 1970 (Box 245)
  - A List of Published and Processed Reports, October 1955-1956: Research in foods, human nutrition and home economics at the land-grant institutions (Box 245)
  - Women's rights pamphlets (Box 245)
  - Staffing American Colleges and Universities (Box 245)
  - Whose Goals for American Higher Education?, 1967 (Box 245)
  - Higher Adult Education in the United States: The Current Picture, Trends, and Issues, 1969 (Box 245)
  - The Youth We Haven't Served, 1966 (Box 245)
  - Community Development: A Directory of Academic Curriculums Throughout the World, 1969 (Box 245)
  - A Listing of Data Collection Instruments for Use in Research in Home Economics Education: 1962-1969 (Box 245)
  - Home Economics Research Assessment Planning Projections Report, 1978-04 (Box 245)
  - A History: 60 Years of Cooperative Extension Service in Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 245)
  - Home Economics Heritage in Tennessee, 1909-1959 (Box 245)
  - Perspectives for the Home Economics Profession (Box 245)
  - Survey and Evaluation of Consumer Education Programs in the United States, 1970 (Box 245)
  - The Consumer Education Information System and Technical Assistance Services of the AHEA, 1978 (Box 245)
  - Consumer Education in Lincoln High School, 1965 (Box 245)
  - Legislation for Consumer and Homemaking Education: Social Implications, 1978 (Box 245)
  - Consumer Education and Home Economics in the Secondary Schools (AHEA), 1945 (Box 245)
  - International Consumer, 1963 (Box 245)
  - Consumer Guidance and Home Management Education in U.S.A., 1951-1952 (Box 245)
  - Consumer Education Project: Final Report, Education Commission of the States, 1979-02 (Box 245)
  - Teacher's Guide to Financial Education, 1967 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Education for Low-Income Families: A Limited Survey of Programs and Resources, 1964 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Education Bibliography, September 1967 (Box 218)
  - When You Use Credit...for the Family, January 1965 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Information Sources (Box 218)
  - How Families Use Their Incomes (Box 218)
  - Consumer and Homemaking Education Today: An Analysis (Box 218)
  - Assessment of Consumer and Homemaking Education, 1978-02 (Box 218)
  - Federal Trade Commission pamphlets, 1960-1972 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Conference of Greater Cincinnati, 1934-1956 (Box 218)
  - The War on Poverty: The Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 (Box 218)
  - The Statutes: Federal Trade Commission Act (Box 218)
  - Strategy of Change: Summary of Joint Conference on Children and Youth, 1964 (Box 218)
  - Change Agent: The New Role for Consumer and Homemaking Education in California, 1970 (Box 218)
  - Health Care Practices and Perceptions: A Consumer Survey of Self-Medication, 1984 (Box 218)
  - American National Standard: Dimensions, Tolerances, and Terminology for Home Cooking and Baking Utensils, 1978 (Box 218)
  - A Reading List on Funerals (Box 218)
  - Speaking Frankly-a Plain Talk about Funeral Service, 1940 (Box 218)
  - Selected Proceedings, Council on Consumer Information, 1963 (Box 218)
  - Helping Families Manage Their Finances, 1963 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Credit Packet, 1966 (Box 218)
  - The President's Committee on Consumer Interests: A Summary of Activities, 1964-1967 (Box 218)
  - A Department Store in the Classroom, 1969 (Box 218)
  - Credit Cards: Thirty Days to Reality, August 1967 (Box 218)
  - Capsules of Consumer Legislation, March 1969 (Box 218)
  - Things You Should Know About Consumer Credit, August 1967 (Box 218)
  - Home and Family Programs: Wise Use of Credit (Box 218)
  - Home Economics Contribution to Housing Research, 1979 (Box 218)
  - Articles on consumer education, 1941, 1969 (Box 218)
  - "Wrinkle Recovery of Fabrics: Appearance Method", 1968 (Box 218)
  - Proceedings of 25th annual conference of the American Council on Consumer Interests, 1979 (Box 218)
  - A Discussion of Family Money: How Budgets Work and What They Do, 1962 (Box 218)
  - Methodology of Consumer Expenditures Surveys, 1968 (Box 218)
  - The Most for their Money, 1965 (Box 218)
  - References and Summaries of Standards, Specifications and Test Methods for Selected Consumer Commodities, 1937 (Box 218)
  - Consumer Credit and the Low Income Consumer, 1969 (Box 218)
  - Teaching Consumer Education and Financial Planning, 1969 (Box 218)
  - Your Guide for Teaching Money Management, 1965 (Box 218)
  - Designs for Low-Cost Wood Homes, 1969 (Box 218)
  - Space Standards for Household Activities, 1962 (Box 218)
  - Laundry Areas: Space Requirements and Locations, 1957 (Box 218)
  - The Cornell Kitchen, 1952 (Box 218)
  - Focus on Furniture: An Important Element in Housing, 1971 (Box 218)
  - Components of Home Management in Relation to Selected Variables, 1970 (Box 218)
  - History of Family Economics Research, 1862-1962 (Margaret I. Liston), 1993 (Box 218)
  - Pamphlets on consumer credit and law (Box 218)
  - The Pattern of the Years (Dept. of Home Economics, New Mexico State University) (Box 218)
  - Families of the Future (College of Home Economics, Iowa State University), 1972 (Box 218)
  - The IHEA History (Indiana HEA), 1972 (Box 218)
  - Values and Family Ecology by Beatrice Poolucci (1973)and course syllabi(College of Human Ecology, Michigan State University), 1969-1971 (Box 308)
  - Families with Handicapped Members (College of Human Ecology, Michigan State University), 1982 (Box 218)
  - Human Ecology: Meaning and Usage (College of Human Ecology, Michigan State University), 1983 (Box 218)
  - Interdisciplinary Consumer Research, 1980 (Box 218)
  - Evaluating New-Product Proposals, 1973 (Box 218)
  - Instructor's Manual to Accompany Miller's Economic Issues for Consumers, 1978 (Box 218)
  - America's Tastemakers: A new strategy for predicting change in consumer behavior, 1959-04 (Box 218)
  - Domestic Policy Review of Solar Energy, 1979-02 (Box 218)
  - Proceedings of National Nutrition Education Conference, 1971 (Box 218)
  - Nutrition, Your Children, and You (Box 218)
  - Nutrition Study Manual, 1972 (Box 218)
  - An Evaluation of the Pilot Food Certificate Program in Chicago, Illinois and Bibb County, Georgia, 1971-04 (Box 218)
  - Supplement to the Exchange Lists (Box 218)
  - Nutrient Labeling Research, Consumer Research Institute, 1971 (Box 218)
  - Average Weight of a Measure Cup of Various Foods, March 1977 (Box 218)
  - Various nutrition handouts (Box 218)
  - Food Selection for Good Nutrition in Group Feeding, 1971-02 (Box 218)
  - Nutrición Sus Niños y Usted, 1974 (Box 218)
  - Wisconsin Home Economics Conceptual Structure and Planning Guide (Box 218)
  - What People Will Need to Know in the 80s and Beyond to be Intelligent Consumers and Effective Homemakers-by Elizabeth Simpson, University of Wisconsin, 1981-02 (Box 308)
  - Developing Insights into Aging, 1978 (Box 218)
  - History of a College: from Woman's Course to Home Economics to Human Ecology, 1873-1988 (Box 218)
  - Parenting and Children publications, 1938-1950s (Box 218)
  - Marriage-various publications, 1940s-1950s (Box 218)
  - Indiana Curriculum Guide for Human Development, 1979 (Box 229)
  - Instruments for Assessing Selected Professional Competencies for Home Economics Teachers, 1978 (Box 229)
  - North Scott Junior High School Living Skills - Home and Family Curriculum and Instruction Study, Summer 1980 (Box 229)
  - New York State Home Economics Association and New York State Association of Extension Home Economists Legislative Workshop, 1977 (Box 229)
  - Consumer Credit Workshop (Box 229)
  - Student Handbook for the Profession of Dietetics, 1977 (Box 229)
  - Winning FFA Speeches: Principles of Speech Preparation and Presentation, 1976 (Box 229)
  - Leadership Skills You Never Outgrow: Leader's Guide, August 1986 (Box 229)
  - Leadership Skills You Never Outgrow: Leadership Project Book I, II, III, IV, August 1986 (Box 229)
  - Kansas State University Receipt Book and Household Manual, 1968 (Box 229)
  - Current Topics in Food and Nutrition, 1970 (Box 229)
  - What is Home Economics Education?, 1980 (Box 229)
  - General home economics education, 1953, 1961, circa 1970 (Box 229)
  - Youth home economics education, circa 1930-1960 (Box 229)
  - Studies of Home Economics in High School and Adult Education Programs, 1955-1958 (Box 229)
  - Adult home economics education, circa 1940-1959 (Box 229)
  - Publications on cooperative extension service, 1958-1959 (Box 229)
  - Vocational education publications, 1945-1961 (Box 229)
  - Vocational Home Economics Education-Coalitition Statement, 1979 (Box 138)
  - Vocational education publications, 1963-1966 (Box 229)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: Middle/Junior High Occupational Home Economics, 1981 (Box 229)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: Middle/Junior High Consumer and Homemaking, 1981 (Box 229)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: High School Occupational Home Economics, 1981 (Box 229)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: Postsecondary Occupational Home Economics, 1981 (Box 230)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: Adult Consumer and Homemaking, 1981 (Box 230)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: High School Consumer and Homemaking, 1981 (Box 230)
  - Standards for Vocational Home Economics Education: Adult Occupational Home Economics, 1981 (Box 230)
  - Vocational education from AIM: 1967-1971 (Box 230)
  - Educational and Vocational Goals of Youth (North Carolina; South), 1967-1968 (Box 230)
  - Model for Change with Emphasis on Pre-Vocational Education Home Economics, 1968 (Box 230)
  - General vocational education and curriculum, 1968, 1970 (Box 230)
  - Cooperative Vocational Education, 1969 (Box 230)
  - Publications on vocational home economics education, 1969-1971 (Box 230)
  - Publications on vocational education, 1973-1976, 1986-1987; 4 folders (Box 230)
  - Common Core Curriculum for Vocational Education, 1977 (Box 230)
  - Interrelationships Among Selected Aspects of Home Economics and Vocational Education, 1978 (Box 230)
  - Indiana Curriculum Guide for Human Development, 1979 (Box 230)
  - North Scott Senior High School Home Economics Curriculum and Instruction Study, 1983-06 (Box 230)
  - Publications on career education, 1972 (Box 230)
  - The Placement of Home Economics Content in Junior and Senior High Schools, 1927 (Box 230)
  - Publications on home economics in high schools, general education, circa 1930-1969 (Box 230)
  - Bulletin of the National Association of Secondary-School Principals, December 1964 (Box 230)
  - Notes on Graduate Studies and Research in Home Economics and Home Economics Education, 1940-1941 (Box 230)
  - Titles of Completed Theses in Home Economics and Related Fields in Colleges and Universities of the United States, 1942-1962; 2 folders (Box 250)
  - List of Published and Processed Reports, 1954-1955; 1955-1956 (Box 250)
  - STEP: Supervising Teacher Enrichment Practices, 1975; 5 folders (Box 250)
  - Publications on teaching home economics, 1976 (Box 250)
  - Publications on home economics teaching techniques, 1976-1978, 1988 (Box 250)
  - Bibliography in Home Economics Education, 1966-1976 (Box 250)
  - Home Economics Teacher Preparation (Box 250)
  - Secondary Education Curriculum Study, 1966 (Box 250)
  - Program Development for Occupational Education: A Report of a National Leadership Seminar on Home Economics Education, 1966 (Box 250)
  - Appraisal of Curriculum Materials Developed for Use by Secondary Home Economics Teachers, 1966 (Box 250)
  - Materials and guides for teachers of home economics, 1967-1969 (Box 250)
  - Publications on teaching values and attitudes, 1969-1972 (Box 250)
  - Publications of the Institute of Higher Education, 1963, 1968 (Box 250)
  - Publications on post-secondary education in home economics, 1967-1968 (Box 250)
  - Publications on plans and programs for higher education in home economics, 1981, 1986 (Box 250)
  - Publications on graduates in home economics education, 1964-1965 (Box 250)
  - Home economics enrollment data, 1965-1968 (Box 250)
  - Ethics in Today's World, 1987 (Box 250)
  - Proceedings of the Conference on Current Concerns in Home Economics Education, 1978 (Box 250)
  - Education for a Changing World of Work, 1963 (Box 250)
  - Current Development in Vocational Home Economics Education, 1970 (Box 250)
  - Selected Highlights in Vocational Home Economics Education, 1973 (Box 250)
  - A Suggested Training Program: Family Dinner Service Specialist, 1964 (Box 250)
  - A Suggested Training Program: The Homemaker's Assistant, 1964 (Box 250)
  - A Suggested Training Program: Management Aide in Low-Rent Public Housing Projects, 1964 (Box 250)
  - A Suggested Training Program: Clothing Maintenance Specialist, 1964 (Box 250)
  - A Suggested Training Program: Hotel and Motel Housekeeping Aide, 1964 (Box 250)